const STORE = {
    questions: [
       {
         question: "Why do cats have whiskers?",
         options: [
               "It is extra-grown hair that is a little bit stronger",
               "To keep bugs off there face",
               "To see if they can get through a small space",
               "For better smell"
         ],
         answer: "To see if they can get through a small space"
       },

       {
         question: "Do cats swivel their ears back?",
         options: [
             "No",
             "Yes",
             "Only when noise is made",
             "When they are sleeping"
         ],
         answer: "Yes"
       },

       {
           question: "Can most cats climb down a tree they got into?",
           options: [
                "Maybe",
                "No",
                "Yes",
                "Cats don't climb trees"
           ],
           answer: "No"
       },

       {
           question: "Why can't cats normally climb down trees they get into?",
           options: [
                "They don't want to",
                "They are to afraid",
                "Their claws are curved",
                "The get comfortable in the tree"
           ],
           answer: "Their claws are curved"
       },

       {
           question: "Are cats nocturnal?",
           options: [
                "Yes",
                "No",
                "Only at night",
                "Only in different seasons"
           ],
           answer: "No"
       },

       {
           question: "Why do cats have a tail?",
           options: [
                "To run fast",
                "They need it for balance",
                "They're spine was to long",
                "To make them look cute"
           ],
           answer: "They need it for balance"
       },

       {
           question: "What are haunches?",
           options: [
                "Shoulders",
                "Lower front legs",
                "Lower back legs",
                "The curve in their back"
           ],
           answer: "Lower back legs"
       },

       {
           question: "Why do cats have sandpaper tongues?",
           options: [
                "To get meat off of bones",
                "To clean wounds",
                "To drink water",
                "To clean them selves"
           ],
           answer: "To drink water"
       },

       {
           question: "Why do cats scratch furniture or trees?",
           options: [
                "To hurt your feelings",
                "Because they don't know any better",
                "To mark their territory",
                "To shave their nails down"
           ],
           answer:  "To mark their territory"
       },

       {
           question: "What does it mean when a cat slowly blinks?",
           options: [
                "They are relaxed",
                "They are comfortable",
                "Because they love you",
                "They are sleepy"
           ],
           answer: "Because they love you"
       }
    ],
    currentQuestion: 0,
    score: 0
};
